[Too Young To Love]
[Episode 19]
Lan!
What happened?
How are you feeling?
I'm just feeling a bit...
nauseous.
Come on, slowly.
Let me help you up.
I'm a bit nauseous,
and having a pain in the head.
Is...
your stomach hurting?
Yes, it is.
Put on my scarf. Don't catch a cold.
That's a lot.
How much longer will it take?
The nurse said you would be on the drip
till tomorrow morning.
It's the flu season now.
You should stay warm.
Put it back on.
Or you might catch a cold too.
I'm fine.
Wait here for a second.
You bought that many heat packs?
Yes.
With these,
you won't feel cold anymore.
Come on.
I'm starting to sweat.
That's the whole point.
Sweating means you're recovering.
There's a hot water bottle too.
Your feet must be freezing, aren't they?
Let it stay here for a while,
and your feet will warm up.
There's also water.
It's a bit too hot now.
Wait till it cools down.
Tell me when you feel like drinking it.
I'll pour you some then.
Xiaole, you're so nice.
You're treating me so well.
I promise I'll repay you
by treating you very, very well too.
How do you repay me
when you're sick like this?
Sleep now.
Goodnight.
Are you tired?
How could I possibly be tired?
But I think you are.
How about...
you sleep in the bed with me?
I want to lean on you.
Well then...
fine.
Easy.
I'd hate to squish you.
Your hand.
Why does it feel so cold?
Is it?
Sleep now.
You'll be well when you wake up tomorrow.
Okay.
My baby, go to sleep.
Miss Luo,
you had too much to drink.
Come on.
Get in my car. I'll drive you home.
I can manage on my own.
Just come with me.
He must've overslept.
The editor-in-chief will be back tomorrow.
Haven't you long been interested
in the overseas division?
I'll introduce you to him tomorrow.
Remember, that's your only opportunity.
Gosh, I'm screwed.
I've screwed it all up.
Hello, Xiaole.
Ma.
I...
I don't think I can make it to the office
today.
Xiaole,
our editor-in-chief values integrity.
If you stand him up this time,
you'll hardly get another chance
to meet him.
I-I know. I understand.
But I'm afraid...
I really can't arrive in time.
Sorry.
What's more important than your meeting
with the editor-in-chief?
Others don't even have
such an opportunity.
This could be a big break in your career.
I know this is a great opportunity,
and I deeply appreciate your help, Ma.
However...
I really need to attend to an emergency
at home.
I'm sorry.
I bought you breakfast.
Steaming hot porridge.
Have you eaten yet?
Yes, I have.
Come on, sit up. Careful.
Slowly.
Is it good?
After you finish the porridge,
I'll take you back to campus.
You should spend the next couple days
resting in your dorm.
Aren't you supposed to meet
the editor-in-chief this morning?
I'm fine on my own.
It's okay.
Don't worry about me.
I can handle it.
No. I can go back to campus myself.
It's time you left.
I've got it all planned out.
Don't worry.
But this opportunity is very important
to you.
Really, it's okay.
We have already...
rescheduled...
the meeting.
Is it true?
True as told.
I'll meet him another day.
Good then.
Eat up.
Is it good?
Yeah.
I feel like I'm alive again.
[Lutao Free Restaurant]
You've been waiting, right?
Did you get rained on?
[Lutao Free Restaurant]
Such heavy rain.
How about a drink at my place
till the rain stops?
Okay. Let me
give you a ride then. I drove here.
Yu,
go home and get some rest.
Okay, I'm leaving now.
What are you doing here?
The forecast said it would rain,
so I came to pick you up.
Where's the rain?
It'll be raining soon. Do you believe it?
Let's go.
[U-turn permitted
at the intersection ahead]
This is the fifth New Year
we've spent together.
Time is really...
flying.
Yeah.
Come on.
Let's celebrate.
Happy New Year.
I...
have
something to ask of you.
What is it?
Move in with me.
What?
I'd love to...
see you every morning
when I wake up.
I mean it.
Wait a second.
Why?
I need to give you something important.
Rings.
Let me put one on you.
Agreed?
It just slipped onto my finger.
Yes.
That ring just obeyed my order.
Fireworks!
No one's around.
Come here.
Let me help you put on the gloves.
It's a bit cold today.
We single people are so jealous of you.
Where is Zhao Zhenghao?
Why is he late every year?
I'm here, aren't I?
You missed me, didn't you?
Look.
What a load!
Did you just empty
an entire fireworks shop?
Where is Fan?
How come he's even later than me?
I'll call him and rush him.
Don't.
Just stand away.
Ning, over here!
Long time no see.
Ning.
What happened?
Did Fan and Luo Ningzi break up?
Shut up.
Are they picking sides now?
It can't be that serious, right?
Chen Fan and I will solve
the problems between us.
Let's set off the fireworks.
Perhaps Chen Fan is too busy dealing with
his own business to come here.
I doubt that.
He puts
romantic relationships above all things.
A breakup is like the end of the world
to him.
Alright.
It's getting late.
Let's set off the fireworks now.
Or we'll miss the New Year's Eve dinner.
Come on.
Set off the fireworks.
Here you are,
Ning.
Thanks.
Put on some music to liven things up.
Let me see.
How about this song?
I've heard it before.
It's viral on the internet.
I think it's a creation
♪ Dusk gently fell on the coastline ♪
of...
an independent band called the God of War.
♪ The quietly passing breeze
gave the clouds a kiss ♪
The singer's voice sounds
just like Chen Fan's.
Yes, it does.
♪ The Earth keeps spinning round ♪
Has it ever occurred to you
that given Chen Fan's talent,
♪ Painted with shades of romance ♪
♪ That was the moment I met you ♪
it's a piece of cake
for him to write a song like this?
♪ Even mountains and seas
can't separate us ♪
I just realized
♪ I wish I could turn into a bird
to explore the world for you ♪
something came up at the place
of my part-time job.
I need to hurry back there now.
♪ The vast, boundless Milky Way ♪
I'll call you in a few days.
♪ Sings its tender serenade ♪
Happy New Year.
♪ I can't live a second without you ♪
Ning...
Stay safe!
♪ Looking forward
to the next beautiful dream ♪
♪ I just want to be with you ♪
♪ To see the most romantic starry sky
together ♪
[Super Hero Fan]
♪ The evening breeze tells
heartfelt emotions ♪
[Cai Yu] [Refuse] [Answer]
♪ All the stars surround you ♪
♪ The moon smiles at you ♪
♪ I give you all the good things
in the world ♪
[Super Hero Fan]
♪ And the light in your eyes ♪
♪ Shines like diamonds ♪
♪ Drawing an exclamation mark
in my world ♪
♪ The evening breeze embraces you ♪
Alright.
As usual,
♪ And I run towards you ♪
let's make wishes!
I want a boyfriend!
♪ I hear our passionate heartbeats ♪
Why do you want a boyfriend again?
♪ We borrow a dream ♪
♪ To build a castle ♪
I hope the ones I love will all stay
♪ Every star is a romantic symbol ♪
safe and healthy!
That'll come true!
♪ Let me find you ♪
Xiaole, make a wish.
Who is setting off fireworks up there?
Why is Mr. Hu still
patrolling during the New Year?
-Time to run.
-Let's go.
♪ Even mountains and seas
can't separate us ♪
Stop!
Stop there!
♪ I wish I could turn into a bird
to explore the world for you ♪
Don't you dare run!
They're going towards the canteen.
♪ The vast, boundless Milky Way ♪
♪ Sings its tender serenade ♪
♪ I can't live a second without you ♪
♪ Looking forward
to the next beautiful dream ♪
What a shame that we didn't get to watch
the fireworks for a longer time.
♪ I just want to be with you ♪
♪ To see the most romantic starry sky
together ♪
How did you get this?
I stuffed it in my pocket
during the chaos.
♪ The evening breeze tells
heartfelt emotions ♪
You're so brilliant.
♪ All the stars surround you ♪
♪ The moon smiles at you ♪
Let me put it here.
♪ I give you all the good things
in the world ♪
I'm too scared to light it. You do it.
♪ And the light in your eyes ♪
Step back, will you?
♪ Shines like diamonds ♪
Sure.
-Stay back.
-Yes.
♪ Drawing an exclamation mark
in my world ♪
♪ The evening breeze embraces you ♪
♪ And I run towards you ♪
♪ I hear our passionate heartbeats ♪
Make a wish! Make a wish now!
♪ We borrow a dream ♪
♪ To build a castle ♪
Oh, right.
It's time to make a wish.
I wish for Tong Xiaole and Yi Lan
to be together for ever and ever!
♪ Every star is a romantic symbol ♪
Consider that little wish granted!
♪ Let me find you ♪
Happy New Year!
I can't believe
you came back for the fireworks.
Cheapskate.
These fireworks could be a fire hazard
here.
I should be responsible for their disposal
since I brought them here.
You're as responsible as ever.
And you're as pretty as ever.
You do have a good eye.
By the way,
you just said
you wanted a new boyfriend.
Did anything happen?
No.
I just don't think
I dated the right person before.
But in my opinion,
one shouldn't stop pursuing true love
just because of a bad romance.
I still believe in love.
Yeah, I agree.
If you are to get into a relationship
with someone,
you should definitely have
a lot of information
of him or her first.
Yeah.
That's how it should work,
right?
You're making it sound so simple.
Have you met your true love?
Me?
Yeah.
Well, I'm just a natural giver.
I would put whoever I'm dating first.
However,
that always makes me seem annoying.
But I actually like men of your type.
I think they're great.
I'd love to have a considerate boyfriend.
What's wrong?
Give it to me.
Don't get burned.
You should've been careful.
It's okay.
I'll put a Band-Aid on it later.
Zhao Zhenghao.
Shall we try dating?
Tong, you can't h-hold your liquor.
Cut the crap.
No, no, no. I mean...
I did have drinks just now!
You call that drinking?
Keep it down, you guys.
You...
It's New Year's.
Why should we keep it down?
I need one more drink!
Hold on.
Wait, I just remembered something.
Steady. W-What now?
Red envelopes.
We're giving red envelopes too.
-I have some to give as well.
-Son!
My love!
Thank you, Dad!
We have some too.
Here you are.
Give them to the children.
Thank you, Dad!
Xiaole!
Thank you, Uncle Dong.
Be good.
-Thank you, Uncle.
-Here you are.
This is yours, Xiaole.
Happy New...
Year!
My dear brother-in-law,
will you give me your red envelopes?
Who are you calling "brother-in-law"?
If you call me "brother-in-law" every year
from now on,
I'll give you red envelopes each year.
I have four red envelopes now!
We've had it settled.
The two of us will...
w-w-will go for a drink later.
"Brother-in-law"?
So what should I call you now?
[Lutao Free Restaurant]
Isn't it simplicity itself?
You just pick
a school you like.
Then I'll ask a professor
to write you a recommendation letter.
As for the tuition fees,
my foundation will sponsor you.
Mr. Guo,
I mean...
Can I
take this money from you as a loan?
I'll pay you back
when I return from abroad.
We can even sign a contract on that.
You are a smart girl.
I bet you know
how to seize an opportunity.
What I'm offering you
is not just money,
but also a springboard
that allows you
to jump to a higher place
and to see further.
Drink it up.
Let me do it.
Miss Luo.
Mr. Guo,
please,
consider the money a loan.
I'd hate to owe you a favor
for this money.
I just love your personality.
But you should know,
there is no such thing as a free lunch
in this world.
Mr. Guo,
just let her
mull it over.
Today,
we're here to enjoy a nice dinner
and some fine wine.
Come on. Let's toast to Mr. Guo.
Cheers, Miss Luo.
You can really hold your liquor, Miss Luo.
Let me fill your glass.
I can't drink anymore.
These are
the two last glasses.
Propose a toast.
Cheers.
A great drinker, isn't she?
Not bad.
Let's have more.
Mr. Shang,
a toast to you.
[Hotel]
[Lutao Free Restaurant]
Quite a dedicated manager, isn't he?
He's already waiting.
Thanks for coming, everyone.
Everything is set.
Please come in.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Everyone!
Let's give a big round of applause
to welcome this band, the God of War!
Yu, give me a break.
Whether your dreams
will come true or not depends on tonight.
If you miss it,
you'll miss everything.
Get a move on.
I...
I can't drink anymore.
Just come with me.
Come on.
Stop resisting, alright?
Let's go.
No, I refuse.
Move!
Who is it?
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Wang!
He's making a scene in public.
Kick him out!
Cai Yu, you brat,
causing me trouble again, aren't you?
I went to great lengths
to invite Mr. Chen over.
You must apologize to him now.
Wait.
I'm the one to apologize?
Of course you are.
Mr. Chen comes to watch your performance
every night.
Frankly speaking,
I wanted to replace you guys long ago.
Yet Mr. Chen insisted that you stay.
Now it's not too late
to replace them.
Cai Yu,
get out.
Now!
I'm not leaving.
[Hotel]
[Lutao Free Restaurant]
Hello, Professor Ye.
Luo Ningzi.
That overseas exchange program slot
is yours now.
Tuition is waived,
and there's a scholarship for you.
Congratulations.
Your hard work has paid off.
Great job getting through this period.
[Lutao Free Restaurant]
As expected,
cramming wouldn't
get me through the interview.
I've always known Ning is amazing.
She got that one and only
exchange program slot.
She's really something.
How about...
we go study abroad too?
I happen to want to pursue further studies
in photography.
You'll go with me?
Yeah.
Let's go wherever
you want to go.
Okay?
How very kind of you!
[When the sun goes down,
it's time to drink]
♪ All the stars surround you ♪
♪ The moon smiles at you ♪
♪ I give you all the good things
in the world ♪
♪ And the light in your eyes ♪
♪ Shines like diamonds ♪
♪ Drawing an exclamation mark
in my world ♪
♪ The evening breeze embraces you ♪
♪ And I run towards you ♪
♪ I hear our passionate heartbeats ♪
♪ We borrow a dream ♪
♪ To build a castle ♪
♪ Every star is a romantic symbol ♪
♪ Let me find you ♪
Thank you for protecting me
last time.
I just happened to be there.
It was a small favor.
Don't mention it.
You've changed quite a lot.
In what way?
I can't name it.
But in general,
you've changed for the better.
It's all thanks to you.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have been
able to find my...
life goal.
Anyway,
seeing you're doing well in everything,
I'm relieved.
I heard you would study abroad soon.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
And I wish you
all the best.
Lan,
I'm heading abroad soon.
I didn't tell you earlier
because I didn't want you
to get too sentimental.
Take good care of yourself.
I'll be back in no time.
Chen Fan,
I am...
going abroad soon.
When we met up the other day,
there were things
I couldn't bring myself to say.
But anyway, you're a really nice guy.
I should've cherished...
what we had before.
I wish you all the best.
Chen Fan,
I am... going abroad soon.
When we met up the other day,
there were things
I couldn't bring myself to say.
But anyway, you're a really nice guy.
I should've cherished...
what we had before.
I wish you all the best.
Okay, roger that.
What now?
Are you leaving?
How about I see you off?
Okay.
I'm not sure
when we'll see each other again.
I hope when we do,
we'll still be friends.
Does that message you just sent me
mean you regret breaking up with me?
Among all emotions,
regret is the most meaningless to me.
But for what it's worth,
you're a really nice person.
We just didn't meet at the right time,
and I didn't cherish you enough.
My application
to be a self-funded exchange student
has also been approved.
I think I'm going to the same country
as the one you're heading to.
Yes, I admit
that I was indeed...
a bit immature in the past.
Come to think about it, at that time,
maybe what you really needed
was someone who could fight alongside you.
Over these years,
I've been trying hard
to prove myself.
Now, I think I deserve...
a second chance with you, do I?
Well...
Seems like we two international students
will have to
stick together abroad.